

# Ali Navidi Sari, Iran → +989339668289 2 years of experience ali\_navidi24@yahoo.com

Portfolio: westernal.me/ Blog: dev.to/westernal westernal ali-navidi-850a80209

westernal 🕊 ali-navidi 🖹

Junior Front-End Developer

I'm a 22 years old frontend developer and nearly computer engineering graduate, I've been coding since 2018 and I have 2 years of experience in developing websites, I love to learn more everyday and be a better human/developer.

Skills: (Next.js JavaScript TypeScript SEO Git Bootstrap Remix **c** ) React.js HTML CSS Node.js Cypress Express.js MongoDB Svelte Java Tailwind GraphQL Python

# Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Oben Origin co.

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

# Projects

### social-media-frontend

www.westernal.net/ github.com/westernal/social-media-frontend

Westernal: a full stack social media based on songs

JavaScript, CSS, Cypress, Next.js

### social-media-backend

Westernal: a full stack social media

JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

# Cinema

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Watching and downloading movies website and progressive web app (PWA) with Next.JS and TypeScript

TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

## sari-sarte

Sari-sartel: a mobile and accessories shop.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

## Dashboard

Admin dashboard using Next JS

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

# Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

# **Publications**

# Introducing Westernal: A social media based on songs

**DEV Community** 

## dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9

## How do you write your CSS?

**DEV** Community

dev.to/westernal/how-do-you-write-your-css-3pg2

# Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced